Why can't I go here?
We visited Island Park!
Yay!
Thank you!
I've always wanted to go to an amusement park.
I'm going to have a lot of fun!
I'm going to have fun!
Let's go!
We're going to ride the screams from the very first ride!
Nothing but screams!
Yes! What? ! Fishing pond! Fishing pond! Fishing pond!
Oh, my gosh! Fishing pond!
I want to fish so bad!
But it's a fishing pond, so there's not much action.
You have to do it like this.
So I'm just gonna dive in and get it.
Where do you start? This one.
We're just going to ride the F2 roller coaster.
What color is F2? Green?
Well, doesn't it look pretty bad?
Might be a hard one to start with.
Yeah, it's bad.
It's pretty bad.
You're not getting a car?
No, I'll be fine.
Yeah, you're right.
Oh, wow.
Sometimes it's easy to play hide-and-seek.
Sounds like a bad idea.
What do you mean, "a small shop"?
Oh, no! Absolutely not!
What's this?
You should go!
Why?
Get on my ass.
Yeah!
I'm so sorry.
I'm so excited, I can't even get a shiver out of my pants.
They said it's under 200 cm.
Oh, I can't ride it.
What?
Oh, so that's what this is about.
That's what you're saying.
No problem.
2m people can't get on it.
Plenty of room.
There's plenty of room.
Yay!
Oh, it's a little dangerous from here.
I have to send everyone off and pretend to get on
A-ha!
Yay!
I'm so glad I started YouTube.
I'm so happy.
What did you say?
I'm glad you started YouTube.
My hair like this.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm so happy for you.
I couldn't do it before, and I can't do it now.
Yes, I am.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You can't ride Doraemon, Ee-chan!
Can't ride Doraemon
I can't ride Doraemon
It's all coming out
It's all going to come out
Wahhh...
Hopelessness.
Despair
How to make it
Impossible.
I can't.
Are you ready to go?
I'm ready.
Let's go!
Okay!
Oh, no, no, no, no.
This is fun.
I'll do my best.
Yay!
I'm so glad I quit.
I couldn't do it.
I really couldn't.
We're done.
The seatbelt should be open.
What a pseudo-flying experience!
That was fun.
I had to have surgery on my neck.
It was the best time of my life.
Really?
I felt like I was flying.
The view was so beautiful.
It's like a head.It's like a head.
He's coming back.
One lady, one lady, one lady, one lady...
You know, I was really scared at first.
Every time I go on a ride with a scream machine, at first I'm really scared and I really don't want to go on it, but then it's different.
But once I try it, it's different. I think that if you don't take the first step to try anything, you will lose your life.
I'm having fun now. My neck went away.
Wow, it's fun. Thank you very much. Thank you for giving me this holiday, or rather, this happiness.
I can't do it anymore. I've fallen in love with this place.
My brain shook just now. Now my brain is nixugus.
It's a Titan! Eren!
Galdorfer!
Gachoo!
Oh no. I can hear the jinari.
What? Sounds like fun. Want to go for a ride?
Are you scared?
Oh, yeah.
Protect the bike.
I'm going. I'm gonna go out there and try to get first place.
Oh, no.
Extra.
The bonus!
Let's split up.
It's been too long.
Pow!
Oooh.
This is from yesterday, by the way.
New attack.
New one!
Mon-chan just told me to be serious
He's so cute!
He's so cute.
She said it's bad.
There's that guy who likes to text.
I see.
I'll do my best.
Bye-bye.
What team?
The loud team.
What do we do now?
I think we should text them first.
Yeah. - Yeah.
This is...
Oh, no.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Oh, my gosh!
That's great!
Wow, wow, wow!
What team? This is...
Lemondrin.
Lemondrin will go.
Please.
What's that? It's a dead end.
This is a dead end, isn't it?
Is that what I think it is?
We're gonna have to run.
Let's go.
We're clear.
T-Team. - Yes, sir.
Have a lot of fun.
Come on, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
Cat, cat, cat...
I wonder where he's going to be... but he's obviously going to be like a wakame seaweed...
I'm so glad I got your email!
claimed!
Jens!
Don't go here!
Oh, my God!
Where did that come from?
Are you okay?
This is so funny.
You can't escape these bubbles.
Go, go, go, go.
You can't escape it.
Oh, my God!
Oh, man!
Wow!
Oh, my God!
Oh, man!
Come on!
I'm scared!
Awa's present for you.
Bring me a present, Awa.
Bring some bubbles!
present of bubbles for the ogre
me
Is there anyone here who is a bop, or is Mi-chan giving up?
We made it so that it can't be painted somehow or other.
me me
Ouch, I can't catch my breath!
yahoo
pan
Oh no!
water coverI'll get the water.
It's going to step on it suddenly!
We're stepping on the exit!
What?
Oh, it didn't catch.
Daughters...
Daughters→๎
Daughters to ๋relocated to another group.
?
Here it is, matpat.
[Hajime Shacho's ending]
Wow, wow, wow.
A little water
Choo choo choo!
I'll keep it simple.
Yeah, sober.
That's not good!
We're going to get wet!
That sediment from earlier...
I'm scared. I'm scared.
This way!
Hello!
Time to get out of here.
Bye-bye.
Come on, let's go.
Wait. I see the finish line.
I see the finish line.
I see the finish line!
What? What is this?
Do we have to go?
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Ready?
I'm going!
We did it!
Did you see it?
I see it. I see it.
You see it?
Did you see it?
You see?
You're so cute.
Those bubbles were fun.
I see you.
Yay!
So we went around Highland Park in the summer.
What do you like best?
The first roller coaster I rode and the one I rode in the rain.
I love the first roller coaster and the one I rode in the rain!
The bubbles were fun!
It was fun even in the rain.
It was a lot of fun.
Well then, I hope you all come visit Highland Park again this summer!
Thank you so much for coming to visit us!
Thank you so much for coming today!
Please give us a high rating if you like!
That's all!
Lula, Image Coasterlast, Innolly, Mr. Talk, and Negastar.
Thank you very much!
Bye bye!
Come visit us again!
Okay, let's play!
I could play!
I could play.
Bye-bye!
I'll be happy if you come back and play again.